ribbet.com 2017-12-14

# Ribbet.com - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Effective 23rd February 2015  
At Ribbet we take your privacy very seriously. Access, use, and preservation of personal information by Ribbet will only occur to make Ribbet an excellent experience for you. Disclosure of personal information will never occur without your explicit consent. 

#### Does Ribbet use cookies?

Yes, Ribbet sets a cookie to simply streamline the login process. We do not use cookies to track your web surfing or for any other purpose.

#### Are the images I upload to Ribbet public?

No.

#### Can anyone use my image?

No. You own your images! The copyright for your images remains yours, even after you use Ribbet. We will never use your images without your direct consent. If, for example, we want to feature you on our blog we'll contact you before publishing your work. Furthermore, we only view Ribbeted photos that our users have posted to public sites. 

#### Does Ribbet save email addresses?

Ribbet only saves your personal email in order to keep you up-to-date. We don't store the email addresses of anyone you email photos to.

#### Will any of my personal information be shared with 3rd parties?

We will never share any personally identifying information with any third party. Also, if Ribbet is ever involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of any form of some or all of its assets, we will provide you notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to collect certain non-personally identifying information when you visit our web site, such as hashed data, browser type, date and time. This information is collected for the sole purpose of providing advertisements that are likely to be of greater interest to you, and are gathered through the use of cookies, pixels or other technologies. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) and [Networking Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). 

#### Does Ribbet store my Flickr / Picasa Web Albums / Facebook / etc password?

No, your passwords are never revealed to Ribbet. You can also revoke Ribbet's access to these services at any time through your account settings on the service's web site.

#### How do I unsubscribe from the Ribbet newsletter?

Should you no longer wish to receive our emails, you may click on the unsubscribe link within each message received, and/or contact us here.

#### Will this privacy policy change?

As Ribbet evolves, this privacy policy is likely to evolve along with it. We will never reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent. Furthermore we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of our privacy policy in an archive for your review.

We also adhere to the US Safe Harbor Privacy Principles. For more information about the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe harbor principles, see the [Department of Commerce's web site](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor). 

If you've got any questions or concerns, please feel free to contact us via email at support [at] ribbet.com or write to us at: 'Ribbet Privacy Matters', Level 7, 9 Hunter Street, Sydney NSW 2000, Australia 

Ribbet.com is a trading name of Foto Friend Pty Ltd who own and operate this site.
